day 2
good morning
once I wake up
I put 1 sound of this bro
in reality it is to be able to seek a positive frequency
for the things i'm going to do
it's on i can
the world is falling bro
i need to get into a solution frequency
import your conditions
but your decisions
that will determine your future
I'm a coach too much today
beauty we will act
hi all good girl
I always see it at the mall
but EU never
is very strong
can be
can try 1 mix
it goes
please
I will think then
worth
ah people
all right
I wanted
learn about the new release of the complementary AliExpress
continues
this one
is
thank you dear
thank you
great service
until next bye
bye
you where the next food is you know
I wanted you to do like this
by hand
is on
we first take a block of paper in front of you
cut give a blow of karate you are seeing it
when I put it in my hand
the idea is for you to try to destroy
whether it's in the left hand or the right hand
closed
Oh yeah
gives
1 look back there bro
lie you will give 10 mango mano
our you're not on Guy
it was too much bro
there's 1 guy saying there's Rolando 1 thing in a park
and I go there
agorinha
malandro
with my toilet paper
undertake
uh will bora
I can't be in shit But
the shit I don't stay
okay
Rolando there in the money
I got the mine money there
check right old
mine sent the pix
I didn't even look bro
take a look at this pix here man
it's not possible not bro
look at Amanda's pix here
fifty guy
fifty
tale with toilet paper bro
what is happening to you
I can't believe I made it out of 0
now i will rest
1 way to cap this car window here too
when i'm in need
Yes you Just kind of
together people
let's go
now i have money to start doing business
finally
ai tô tired
doidão is we worth it